sportalink.com 2017-06-24

# Welcome to Sportalink

## _Privacy Policy_

### _Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Sportalink.com (“the Website”), we have a few fundamental principles:

• We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 

• We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

• We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

• We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Sportalink.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Sportalink.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Sportalink.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Sportalink.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Sportalink.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments or sharing content on Sportalink.com.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Sportalink.com choose to interact with the Website in ways that require the Website to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that the Website gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide their first name, last name, email address and password. The Website collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Sportalink.com. Sportalink.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Sportalink.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Sportalink.com’s behalf or to provide services available at Sportalink.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Sportalink.com, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Sportalink.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Sportalink.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Sportalink.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sportalink.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Website and have supplied your email address, Sportalink.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Sportalink.com and our products. Sportalink.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Sportalink.com uses cookies to help the Website identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sportalink.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Sportalink.com’s sole discretion. Sportalink.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

_

* * *
